抱歉  你叫什么来着
I'm sorry, I did not quite catch your name.
发生了什么
What happened?
救我
Help me.
不
No!
神奇女侠  绿灯侠
看哪个
Which one?
我不知道
I don't know.
你不用再担心了  好吗
Hey, there's nothing to worry about anymore, okay?
这讲不通
It doesn't make sense.
什么讲不通
What doesn't make sense?
海瑟
Heather.
血迹
The blood.
冰块
The ice.
海瑟发高烧
Heather had a fever,
就泡了个冰水澡  但她现在好转了
so she took a cold bath, but she's better now.
肯定就是这样了
That has to be it.
我不知道那血是哪来的  但是
I don't know where that blood came from, but...
我们看到她了
we saw her.
我们都看到她了  她完全没事
We both saw her. She's totally fine.
那比利呢
What about Billy?
他怎么了
What about him?
他看上去不对劲
He seemed wrong.
他一直都不对劲
Wrong is kind of like his default.
但至少他不是杀人犯
But it's nice to know he's not a murderer,
那可就糟了
because that would've totally sucked.
那是谁
Who... is that?
瞧  这就是为什么你不能只跟迈克待在一起
See, this is why you can't just hang out with Mike all the time.
这是神奇女侠
This is Wonder Woman.
也就是戴安娜公主
AKA Princess Diana.
她来自天堂岛  那是个隐秘岛屿
She's from Paradise Island, which is, like, this hidden island
岛上只有女亚马逊战士
where there are only women Amazon warriors.
放开我  放开我
Let me go! Let me go!
朵丽丝  你得保持冷静  好吗
Doris, we need you to stay calm for us, okay?
-冷静  -我必须回去
- Stay calm. - I have to go back!
我必须回去
I have to go back!
好吧
Okay, so,
你俩想跟我解释一下  苍天在上
you two want to explain to me what in the name of Jesus
这到底是怎么回事
just happened here?
汤姆
Tom!
爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
海瑟
Heather...
亲爱的
sweetie...
不管这怎么回事  不管他把你卷进了什么事
whatever this is, whatever he's got you into,
你都不用这么做的
you don't have to do this.
你可以阻止他
You can stop this.
这是没法阻止的  爸爸
There is no stopping it, Daddy.
你会明白的
You'll see.
不
No.
海瑟  求你  海瑟
Heather, please! Heather!
尽量别动
Try not to move.
不
No.
海瑟
Heather!
老天爷啊
Jesus Christ.
不
No.
No--
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     草草
怪奇物语  第三季 第四集
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     紫夏
第四章
桑拿测试
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
小心
Hey, careful.
Careful.
来
Here.
乔伊
Joyce.
来  来
Here, here, here.
没事的
It's okay.
就这样  好了吗
That's it. Got it?
-给  -我昏过去多久了
- Here. - How long have I been out?
好一阵了
A while.
你时而清醒时而昏沉
You've been drifting in and out.
但我怎么回来的
Yeah, but how did I get here?
很慢
Slowly.
-你最后记得什么  -有个暴徒袭击了我
- What's the last thing you remember? - Some thug attacked me.
-你需要休息  -我没事
- Hey, you need to rest. - No, I'm fine.
-不  你有事  霍普  -我没事
- No, you're not fine, Hop-- - I'm fine. I'm fine.
我的衣服呢
Where are my clothes?
都湿透了
They were soaked.
你认得他吗
I mean, did you recognize him?
-谁  -那个暴徒
- Who? - The thug.
我没看清楚
Well, I didn't get a good look.
他肯定是政府的吧
Well, I mean, he's gotta be government, right?
是啊  但如果是  他为什么要逃走
Yeah, but if he's government, what's he doing slinking around?
他跑什么
W-Why is he running?
我们怎么在下面什么都没发现
You know, why didn't we find anything down there?
我们去问他
Let's ask him.
那是什么
What is that?
他的牌照
His license plate.
-连字符是什么  -是空缺的
- What are the dashes? - Well, they're blanks.
有一个  好像是H还是P的
There was... I think it was either an H or a P
蹭掉了一块
with the part rubbed off.
绝对有个Y
And there was definitely a Y.
绝对的
For sure.
还有个可能是B  但也可能是8
And that, I think, was a B, but it could've been an eight.
还有...等等
And that-- Wait--
你还是继续做售货员吧
I think you should stick to sales.
你不能搜索一下吗
Can't you run a search or something?
我就是觉得你得降低期望
I just think you have to lower your expectations.
这可是州政府机构
I mean, this is a state government agency.
他们得几周才能找到匹配
Gonna take weeks before they find a match.
-几周  -那还是走运
- Weeks? - If we're lucky.
而且
And, I mean,
这人用自己的名字
what are the odds that this guy
注册汽车的几率又有多大
registers a car in his own name?
不是辆车
It wasn't a car.
你穿的什么啊
Uh, what are you wearing?
什么叫不是辆车
What do you mean it wasn't a car?
收到吗
Do you copy?
红色警报
This is a code red.
重复  红色警报
I repeat, this is a code red.
麦克斯  收到吗
Max. Do you copy?
红色警报
This is a code red.
闭
Shut...
嘴
up.
她关掉了
She turned it off.
开什么玩笑
You've got to be kidding me.
我在睡觉  走开
I'm sleeping. Go away.
我是迈克  别挂电话
This is Mike. Do not hang up.
出事了  坏事
Something happened, something bad.
我们的生命可能有危险
Our very lives can be at stake.
-你说什么呢  -来我家
- What are you talking about? - Just come over to my house.
我们会解释的
We'll explain everything.
-什么  -快来
- What? - Hurry.
他说了什么
What did he say?
再呼叫一次达斯汀
Try Dustin again.
他不接
He's not answering.
那就再呼一次
So, try him again.
达斯汀  收到吗
Dustin, do you copy?
重复  红色警报
I repeat, this is a code red.
那张钥匙卡能开门  不幸的是
That keycard opens the door, but unfortunately,
拿钥匙卡的苏联人还拿了枪
the Russian with this keycard also has a massive gun.
不管房间里是什么  不管盒子里是什么
Whatever's in this room, whatever's in those boxes,
他们很不希望被人发现
they really don't want anybody finding it.
但肯定有办法进去的
But there's gotta be a way in.
知道吗
Well, you know...
我可以干掉他
I could just take him out.
-干掉谁  -那个苏联守卫
- Take who out? - The Russian guard.
怎么了  我偷溜到他身后
What? I sneak up behind him,
打昏他  拿到他的钥匙卡  轻松
I knock him out, and I take his keycard. It's easy.
你没听到我说他有挺大枪吗
Did you not hear the part about the massive gun?
达斯汀  我听到了
Yes, Dustin, I did.
所以  我要偷溜过去
And that's why I would be sneaking.
拜托  告诉我  老实说
Well, please, tell me this, and be honest,
你真的  跟谁打赢过吗
have you ever actually... won a fight?
好吧  有一次
Okay, that was one time--
两次  乔纳森  去年
Twice. Jonathan. Year prior?
听着  那不算数
Listen, that doesn't count.
为什么不
Why wouldn't it?
因为他似乎把你打得很惨
Because it looks like he beat the shit out of you.
-那是...  -你嘴唇肿了  鼻子歪了
- It was... - You got a fat lip, crooked nose,
-眼睛肿了  流了好多血  -加起来的话
- swollen eye, a lot of blood... - ...things that all added up...
这可能还真可行
That just might work.
小费
罗宾
Robin.
罗宾  你干什么
Hey, Robin! Hey, what-- what are you doing?
-我需要现金  -那一半是我的
- I need cash. - Well, half of that's mine.
-你去哪  -想办法进那个房间
- Where're you going? - To find a way into that room,
安全的办法
a safe way.
与此同时  你在这儿卖冰淇淋
And, in the meantime, sling ice cream,
乖乖的  别被人揍了
behave, and don't get beat up.
我马上回来
I'll be back in a jiff.
哥们
Oh, dude.
拜托  别舔我的冰淇淋勺啊
Come on, man, not my scooper.
霍金斯邮报
如果中午前他能搞定排版就行
If he gets us the layout by noon, we can.
好  我告诉他
Okay, I'll let him know.
不知道他们会不会那么做
Dunno if they'll go through with it,
但我觉得该告诉你
but I just thought you should know.
南茜
Nancy.
乔纳森
Jonathan.
我在报社干了25年了
I've worked at this paper for twenty-five years.
Twenty-five...
年
years.
我们是小镇报社
Now, we're a small-town paper,
但我们有大报社没有的东西
but we have something the big papers don't have:
信任
trust.
-社区的信任  -汤姆  你可以...
- The trust of our community. - Tom, if you just--
知道我怎么建立这份信任的吗
Do you know how I built that trust?
靠相信一件你们俩
By placing my faith in something
似乎不怎么看重的东西
the two of you don't seem to value a whole lot:
事实
facts.
Facts.
趁这机会  我们谈谈一些事实
So, while we're here, let's go over the facts.
1  你们违背了我停止追查这则报道的命令
Fact one, you disobeyed a direct order to stop pursuing this story.
2  你们冒称是记者
two, you falsely identified yourselves as reporters,
反复欺骗了一位老太太
repeatedly lying to an elderly woman.
3  你们闯进了她家  构成擅闯罪
three, you broke into her home, committing trespass.
4  她差点死在去医院的路上
four, she almost died en route to the hospital.
要不是我们去了  她就真死了
She would've died if we hadn't shown up!
不管那老鼠染了什么病  她显然被传上了
Whatever disease that rat had clearly passed to her--
5  德里斯科尔太太有妄想型精神分裂
Five! Mrs. Driscoll is a paranoid schizophrenic.
你们不知道吧
You didn't know that, did you?
好了
Now...
带病老鼠
disease-carrying rats?
二次瘟疫  你们觉得可信吗
The second coming of the plague? Does this sound credible to you,
还是听上去更像
or perhaps does this sound
一位病重老妇的妄想
more like the delusions of a very sick old lady?
-这我不知道  -她的家人气坏了
- I didn't know that. - Her family's furious.
气到威胁要起诉
So furious, in fact, they've threatened litigation.
-起诉  -疯了吧
- Litigation? - That's crazy.
这我倒是同意
For once, we agree.
这一切都疯了
This is crazy.
事实上  在我的职业生涯里
In fact, in my entire professional career,
从未遇到过这样的事
I've never dealt with anything quite like it.
但希望
But hopefully,
你已经学到了宝贵的教训
hopefully, you've learned something valuable here.
你已经学到
You've learned...
在工作中
how in the workplace,
在现实世界里
in the real world,
你的行为是有后果的
there are consequences to your actions.
这就要说到第六条  也是最后一条
Which brings me to my sixth and final...
事实了
fact.
你们被解雇了
You're fired.
你俩都是
Both of you.
我起初没觉得真有什么
I didn't think it was anything at first.
我觉得我就是不想去相信
I mean, I think I just didn't want to believe it.
我第一次感觉到是看《丧尸出笼》那天
The first time I felt it was at Day of the Dead.
-那晚还断电了  -然后  第二天
- Power went out that night, too. - And then I felt it again
我又在尼尔森农场附近的田野里感到了
at the field near the Nelson farm the next day.
昨天  又在拜耶斯堡外感到了
Then again yesterday outside Castle Byers.
威尔
Will!
是什么感觉
What does it feel like?
几乎像是
It's almost like...
你们知道坐过山车下行的感觉吗
You know when you drop on a roller coaster?
-知道  -嗯
- Sure. - Yeah.
-不知道  -就好像
- No. - It's like...
你身体里的一切
everything inside your body
都突然下沉  但是
is just sinking all at once, but...
这感觉更糟
this is worse.
你的身体
Your body...
发冷  无法呼吸
it goes cold and-- and you can't breathe.
我以前感觉到过
I've felt it before,
只要他靠近时
whenever he was close.
谁靠近时
Whenever who was close?
吸灵魔
The Mind Flayer.
走开
Go away!
我关闭了大门
I closed the gate.
我知道  但是
I know, but...
如果他没走呢
what if he never left?
如果我们把他跟我们关在了一起呢
What if we locked him out here with us?
这是他
This is him.
他的全部
All of him.
但那天在田野里
But, that day on the field,
他的一部分附在了我身上
a part of him attached itself to me.
我妈妈把它弄了出去
My mom got it out of me...
滚出我儿子的身体
Get the hell out of my son!
然后一一关闭了大门
...and Eleven closed the gate.
但我身体里当时还在的那部分
But the part that was still in me,
如果它还在我们世界里呢
what if it's still in our world?
在霍金斯
In Hawkins.
我不懂  一一关闭大门时魔狗都死了
I don't understand. The Demodogs died when El closed the gate.
如果脑子死亡  身体就死亡
If the brain dies, the body dies.
我们不能冒险
We can't take any chances.
我们需要做最坏的打算
We need to assume the worst.
吸灵魔又回来了
The Mind Flayer's back.
是啊  如果真是
Yeah. And if he is,
他肯定还会想再附在谁身上
he'd want to attach himself to someone again.
新我
A new me.
新宿主
A new host.
怎么分辨一个人是不是宿主
How can you tell if someone is a host?
臭猪克莱恩
他在吗
Hey, is he in?
-嗯  他正忙呢  但是  -好极了
- Yes, he's busy at the moment, but-- - Great.
喂
Excuse me.
你还是坐下吧
You should sit down.
不肯听...
...wouldn't listen--
托尼  等等
Tony, hold on.
我...
Let me, uh...
我得  回头打给你了  好
I might have to-- Let me call you back. Okay.
谢谢
Thanks.
-吉姆  -我知道
- Jim. - I know, I know.
你忙呢  我快点说完  我保证
You're busy. I'm gonna make this fast, I promise.
有...
Is there...
什么问题吗
some kind of problem?
有  可以这么说
Yeah. You might say that.
我想查一个人的名字
Um, I'm looking for the name of a guy.
一个人的名字
The name of a guy.
对  你可能认识他
Yeah, I think you might know this guy.
-好吧  -他那天来过
- Okay. - He was here the other day.
骑了摩托
Rides a motorcycle.
高个  方下巴  黑头发
Big build, square jaw, dark hair.
可能是军人  或退役军人
He's probably military, maybe ex-military?
想起什么来了吗
Is this ringing... any bells?
没有
I don't think so.
是吗
Really?
因为就发生在两天前
'Cause it was just two days ago.
在我见到你之前
This was right before I saw you.
-知道吗  -什么
- You know what? - What?
可能是维修工
Could be the maintenance guy.
-维修  -是啊  记不清他叫什么了
- Maintenance. - Yeah. I can't remember his name.
天呐
Oh, God... Uh...
盖里  还是约翰什么的
Gary or John or something.
坎迪丝应该记录了他的名字
Candice will have his name on file.
我们水管有问题  厕所堵什么的
We've had trouble with the plumbing. Clogged toilets and...
水池也是不听话
sinks with minds of their own.
你经常见水管工吗  拉里
You meeting with a lot of plumbers, Larry?
什么
Excuse me?
这人  我见到他时  他是从你办公室走出来的
This guy, when I saw him, he was coming out of your office.
好吧  我可不记得
Okay, well, I don't remember that.
我见过很多人的
I shake a lot of hands, you know?
你记得我逮到你昏倒在藏身处
Do you remember when I caught you passed out in the hideaway
一鼻孔的白粉吗
with all that powder all over your nose?
-记得吗  -吉姆  得了
- You remember? - Jim, come on, now.
你记得我的手下逮到你和坎迪丝像两只兔子似的
Do you remember when my boys found you and Candice going at it
在你的凯迪拉克后座上啪啪吗
like a couple of bunnies in the back of your Cadillac?
你记得吗
Do you remember that?
你妻子记得吗
Does your wife remember that?
你...
You, uh...
你真想玩这个游戏吗
You really wanna play this game?
不是游戏  拉里
Not a game, Lar.
好吧
Okay.
你以前当糖一样吃的药
Those pills you used to swallow like candy.
我记不得了  你有处方吗
I can't recall, did you have a prescription for those?
还有当值饮酒呢
Or how about drinking on duty?
是啊
Yeah.
我们有好些特别有趣的故事呢
We have some real fun stories about that.
只要给《邮报》的汤姆打个电话
One call to Tom at the Post...
你就完了  伙计
and you're done, buddy.
完了
You're gone.
对了
Oh, and, please,
少拿女儿死了的悲惨故事来唬我
don't give me that dead daughter sob story,
我真心不在乎
'cause I just don't care.
如果你不介意
Now, if you don't mind,
我还忙呢
I really am rather busy.
运营主管
Operating directors--
该死
Damn it!
我的鼻子  你打破了我的鼻子
My nose! You broke my goddamn nose!
你朋友昨晚差点杀了我
And your friend almost killed me last night,
我们还没扯平呢
so I'd say we're still not even.
拉里
Larry?
-少废话  拉里  -拉里
- Let's cut the crap, Larry! - Larry!
那人是谁
Who is this guy?
-政府的  军队的  -你犯下大错了
- Is he government? Is he military? -You're making a big mistake.
他是谁
Who is he?
是阿诺德·施瓦辛格
It's Arnold Schwarzenegger.
拉里
Larry!
你要打给谁  警察吗
Who you calling? The police?
戒指真不错  拉里
That is a nice ring you got there, Larry.
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们试试吧
Let's find out.
好好好  冷静
Okay, okay, okay. Be cool, be cool.
我不知道他叫什么  真的
I don't know his name, I swear.
但你认识他
But you know him.
他有时会给我些东西
He... He gives me things sometimes.
什么样的东西
What kind of things?
钱  礼物  赠礼
Money. Presents. Aah! Gifts.
这人是圣诞老人吗
Who is this guy, Santa Claus?
是星庭  他为星庭工作
Starcourt. Starcourt. He works for Starcourt.
-商场  -对
- The mall? - Yes, yes.
是啊
Yeah, right.
我发誓  真是星庭
I swear! I swear! I swear! Starcourt.
他们是商场的东家
They-- They own the mall.
他们想向东霍金斯扩张
They want to expand to East Hawkins.
他们需要地产  土地
They needed property, some land.
有些人不想卖
Some people didn't want to sell,
我就给他们施压  仅此而已
so I leaned on them a little. That's all.
我发誓  仅此而已
I swear, that's all.
-他们要地干什么  -我不知道
- Why do they want this land? - I don't know!
你有交易的记录吗
You have records of these purchases, these, uh...
这些买地交易
these land purchases?
你不想惹这些人的  吉姆
You don't want to mess with these people, Jim.
你还是担心自己吧  拉里
I think you should worry about yourself right now, Larry,
别担心我
not about me.
那些记录
The records.
在哪呢
Where are they?
拉里
Larry?
他就是撞到了头
He just bumped his head.
就是碰了一下  是吧  拉里
Just a little boo-boo, right, Lar?
今天愉快
Have a nice day.
拉里
Larry!
真扯淡
It's bullshit.
汤姆说  德里斯科尔是个精神分裂
So, according to Tom, Driscoll's just a schizophrenic?
而那只老鼠  也没什么特别
And that rat is just a rat?
这都是个大巧合吗
And it's all, what, some big coincidence?
知道我怎么想吗
You know what I think?
我觉得汤姆嗑药了
I think Tom was on drugs.
-什么  -你看到他了吗
- What? - Did you see him?
他大汗淋漓
He was sweating like crazy.
手掌也汗津津的
And his palms were clammy.
他看上去糟透了
He looked awful.
-你觉得好笑吗  -不
- Oh, is this funny to you? - No.
就是觉得不可思议
No, it's just kind of incredible.
不可思议
Incredible?
是啊  不可思议  你总能自圆其说
Yeah, incredible how you just continue to convince yourself.
那什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
我反复叫你别跟踪这则报道了
I told you over and over to drop this story.
说这样不好
That it was a bad idea.
但你不肯听  这下我遭殃了
But you refused, and now, I'm screwed.
只是夏季打工  你的生活没结束呢
It's a summer job. Your life is hardly over.
我可不住在枫树街的二层楼里
I don't live in a two-story house on Maple Street.
我爸不挣六位数
My dad doesn't earn six figures.
他人都不在
Hell, he isn't even around.
天呐  又来《雾都孤儿》这套了
God, here comes the Oliver Twist routine.
按揭  大学学费
Mortgage, college tuition.
那都是真实的东西  南茜
You know, they're real things, Nancy.
你不用在乎  所以你不在乎的东西
Things that you don't care about, only because you don't have to.
-我可没活在泡泡里  -你就是
- I didn't realize I lived in a bubble! - Well, you do!
你希望一切装在银盘子里递给你
You want everything handed to you on a silver platter.
你只是实习生  南茜
I mean, we were interns, Nancy!
实习生
Interns!
你以为呢
What did you expect,
你一个月内就能当上明星记者
that you would make star reporter in a month?
侦破大案吗
Crack the big case?
你知道你口气跟他们一样吧
You sound just like them. You realize that, right?
就跟布鲁斯和那些混蛋一样
Just like Bruce and those assholes--
是啊  那些混蛋给了我们份工作
Yeah, yeah, those assholes gave us jobs.
是吗  那就是羞辱
Is that what that was? That was humiliating.
羞辱
Humiliating.
真实世界很糟
Yeah, the real world sucks.
像我们其他人一样面对吧
Deal with it like the rest of us.
你根本不懂
You don't know what it's like.
你也不懂
Neither do you.
看来我们已经不理解彼此了
Well, then, I guess we just don't understand each other anymore.
看来是的
Yeah, I guess not.
你早回家了
Hey, you're home early.
是啊  今天工作不重
Yeah. Light day.
光靠20块就能在郡记录厅
It is fascinating what 20 bucks will get you
查到的东西真是不可思议
at the County Recorder's Office.
星庭商场
Starcourt Mall.
完整蓝图
The complete blueprints.
不赖
Not bad.
我们在这里  海员勺
So, this is us, Scoops,
我们想去这里
and this is where we want to get.
我看不到通往那里的路
I mean, I don't really see a way in.
是没有
There's not,
如果你光找门的话
if you're talking exclusively about doors.
风道
Air ducts.
正确
Exactly.
原来  这间密室跟常规房间一样需要空气
Turns out, this secret room needs air just like any old room.
而这些气道
And these air ducts
一路通往
lead all the way...
这里
here.
手电筒
Flashlight.
谢谢
Thank you.
不行啊
Yeah, I don't know, man.
你恐怕钻不进来  这里
I don't know if you can fit in here. It's, like...
非常窄
super tight.
我能行
I'll fit.
相信我  没有锁骨  记得吗
Trust me. No collar bones, remember?
什么
Uh, excuse me?
他...有病
Oh, he's, uh... Yeah, he's got some disease.
是叫什么...
Chry, uh... It's chrydo, um...
什么的  我也不知道
Something. Yeah, I dunno.
他少几块骨头什么的  像秋葵一样能伸能屈
He's missing bones and stuff. He can bend like Gumbo.
是甘比吧[绿色黏土小人]
You mean Gumby.
就是秋葵啦
I'm pretty sure it's Gumbo.
-史蒂夫  闭嘴  推我  -好
- Steve, just shut up and push me! - Okay.
我推你
I'll push ya.
-别推脚  蠢蛋  推我屁股  -什么
- Not my feet, dumbass. Push my ass. - What?
碰我屁股  我不在乎
Touch my butt! I don't care!
-使劲点推  -我在推了
- Come on! Harder! - I'm pushing!
使劲推
Push harder!
你在玩我的腿呢
You're playing with my legs.
我没玩  我脚下不稳
I'm not playing, I have terrible footing.
-快点  -我就把你塞进去了  准备好了吗
- Come on! - I'm gonna just shove you, ready?
-塞  -一  二
- Just shove me? - One, two...
-该死  -行吗
- Shit. - That work?
-再来一次  -水手们  需要全员出动
- One more time. - Ahoy, sailors! All hands on deck!
来啊
Come on.
过来给我上样品
Get over here and serve me some samples.
我不知道  我看他挺正常的
I don't know. He looks pretty normal to me.
正常  你见过几次他穿上衣啊
Normal? How many times have you seen him with a shirt on?
是有点奇怪
I mean, it's a little weird.
不止一点
More than a little.
他泡了冰浴  吸灵魔就喜欢冷
He was in a tub with ice. The Mind Flayer likes it cold.
-再加上别的  -但他在泳池边闲坐着呢
- Plus everything else-- - But he's lounging at the pool,
这可一点也不吸灵魔
which is, like, the least Mind Flayer thing ever.
未必
Not necessarily.
吸灵魔喜欢躲藏
The Mind Flayer likes to hide.
他只在需要时利用我
He only used me when he needed me.
就像是  休眠
It's like... like you're dormant.
然后  等他需要你了
And then, when he needs you,
你就被激活了
you're activated.
好吧  那我们
Okay, so we just...
等待他被激活
wait until he gets activated.
不  如果他伤人呢
No. What if he hurts someone?
或是杀人
Or kills someone.
我们不能冒险
We can't take that chance.
我们得搞清楚他是不是宿主
We need to find out if he's the host.
-你去哪  -我有个点子  仅限男生
- Where are you going? - I have an idea. Boys only.
-不是吧  -相信我一次
- Seriously? - Just trust me on this one.
好  我们等到泳池关闭  大家都走光
Okay, so we wait until the pool closes, until everyone leaves,
男宾
我们要想办法让他从这里
and we somehow get him to come from here and...
进入这里
get him into here.
-关门  -小孩  快关门
- Hey, shut the door! - Hey, come on, kid, shut it!
我吐了一点点
I think I just threw up in my mouth.
听着  控制器就在这里  完美
And look, the controls are right here. It's perfect.
-能达到足够的高温吗  -104度呢
- Will it get hot enough? - 220 degrees.
我们只需要想办法把他骗进去
We just have to figure out how to get him in here.
-然后我们锁门  -加热
- Then we lock him in... - Heat him up...
不管怎样  我们都能确定了
No matter what happens, we'll know.
我们能确定无疑
We'll know for sure.
海员勺
-我不知道  -你不知道自己能不能钻进去吗
- Yeah, I don't know. - You don't know if you can fit?
我能钻进去  我不确定我想不想
Oh, I can fit. I just don't know if I want to.
你幽闭恐惧吗
Are you claustrophobic?
我不恐惧什么
I don't have phobias.
-好吧  那怎么了  -就这么了
- Okay, well, what's the problem? - The problem is,
我还没听到你们说
I still haven't heard what's in this
艾瑞卡有什么好处
for Erica.
再来点软糖
More fudge, please.
去吧
Go on.
好了
All right.
你看这个  这就是你要走的路线
You see this? This is the route you're gonna take.
然后我们等到今晚最后的货送走
Then we just wait till the last delivery goes out tonight.
你就打掉隔山  跳下来  开门
Then you knock out the grate, jump down, open the door.
-然后你们就能知道盒子里有什么了  -对
- Then you find out what's in those boxes? - Exactly.
你说守卫有枪
And you say this guard is armed.
对  但他不会在的
Yes, but he won't be there.
-还有陷阱吗  -陷阱
- And booby traps? - Booby traps?
-激光  墙里有尖刺  -什么
- Lasers, spikes in the wall? - What?
知道你们这个半吊子计划在我听来像什么吗
You know what this half-baked plan of yours sounds like to me?
威胁儿童安全
Child endangerment.
我们会时刻用无线电联络你
We'll be in radio contact with you the whole time--
威胁儿童安全
Child endangerment.
艾瑞卡
Erica?
我们认为这些苏联人想伤害我们国家
We think these Russians want to do harm to our country.
搞大破坏  你不爱国吗
Great harm. Don't you love your country?
美国这个单词里里就有"艾瑞卡"
You can't spell "America" without "Erica."
是啊
Uh, yeah, yeah.
好奇怪  但说得没错
Oddly, that's, uh, totally true.
所以  别为了我们
So, so, don't do this for us.
为了你的祖国吧
Do it for your country.
为了你的同胞吧
Do it for your fellow man.
为了美国吧  艾瑞卡
Do this for America... Erica.
我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
I just got the chills.
是啊  因为冰淇淋饮料
Oh, yeah, from this float,
不是因为你的讲话
not your speech.
知道我最喜欢这个国家的什么吗
Know what I love most about this country?
资本主义
Capitalism.
-你知道资本主义是什么吗  -嗯
- Do you know what capitalism is? - Yeah.
-嗯  -就是说  这是自由市场体系
- Yeah. - It means this is a free market system.
就是说  人们提供服务可以收费
Which means people get paid for their services,
具体要看他们的贡献有多宝贵
depending on how valuable their contributions are.
在我看来
And it seems to me,
我能钻进那个小气道的本事
my ability to fit into that little vent
对你们非常重要
is very, very valuable to you all.
所以  要我帮忙
So, you want my help?
这份奶油糖果船
This USS Butterscotch
最好今后还有更多
better be the first of many.
免费冰淇淋
And I'm talking free ice cream
终生享用
for life.
真喜欢这地方  拉里
Wow, I love the place, Lar.
那伙计是你亲手打的吗
Hey, you shoot that fella yourself?
那不是真的
That's-- That's not real.
不是吧
No shit!
好了
All right, so...
这究竟是什么
what exactly are we looking at?
地契  地产转移
Land deeds, transfers of property.
地契转移书
你星庭的朋友们
So your buddies at Starcourt,
他们突然开始大量买地
they suddenly start buying up all this property.
-他们说为什么了吗  -我说了
- They tell you why? - I already told you,
他们什么都不告诉我
they don't tell me anything.
他们只是利用你  我懂
They're just using you, I get it.
我不懂的是
What I don't get
你为什么把一堆地契
is why you have a bunch of land deeds
放在你卧室的保险箱里
in a safe in your bedroom.
这些人  吉姆
These people, Jim,
他们不是好人
they're bad news.
这是勒索资本吗
So, what, this is blackmail?
-是保护  -保护
- Protection. - Protection.
等等
Hold on a second.
怎么了
Hey, what is it?
海斯农场  亨利家
Hess Farm, Henry's place,
布洛克家
Bullocks...
看  都在这里
Look, they're all here.
都在霍金斯东南  乔丹湖附近
They're all in Southeast Hawkins, right near Jordan Lake.
乔丹湖附近还有什么
And what else is near Jordan Lake?
电站
The power plant.
四晚前  发生了大规模断电
Four nights ago, there was a huge power outage,
-次日  -你的磁铁就掉落了
- and the next day-- - Your magnets fell.
斯考特说这台机器
Yeah, I mean, Scott says that this machine
需要大量电力才能运行
would take a massive amount of power to run.
-是啊  -如果这台机器
- Yeah. - So, what if this machine
真的存在
that we've been talking about really does exist,
而我们之所以在实验室没找到它
and the reason that we didn't find it at the lab
是因为它不在实验室  而是在这些地皮上
is because it isn't at the lab, it's at one of these properties.
你还是  别做售货员了
I want you to... forget about sales.
来霍金斯警局给我干吧
I want you to come work for me at the Hawkins PD.
每天看你这张臭脸吗  算了吧
And have to look at your face every day? I don't think so.
拉里
Larry!
你想去哪啊  伙计
Hey, where do you think you're going, pal?
南茜
Nancy?
Nance?
或许乔纳森是对的
Maybe Jonathan's right.
老实说  我没考虑他
To be honest, I wasn't thinking about him.
我都没考虑任何人
I wasn't thinking about anyone, really.
我就...
I just...
我希望我是对的
I wanted to be right.
-我特希望我是对的  -你是对的吗
- I wanted to be right so badly. - And were you?
我以为是
I thought so.
但或许我...
But maybe I just...
不想承认我错了
don't want to admit that I'm wrong,
因为如果我错了
because if I'm wrong,
-那  -你就像大家以为的那样了
- then-- - You're what everyone thinks you are.
只是个不知天高地厚的孩子
Just a kid who has no idea what she's doing.
生活于世不容易  南茜
It's not easy out there, Nance.
我知道
I know.
人们总说你不行
People are always saying you can't.
你不该
That you shouldn't.
你不
That you're not...
够聪明  够厉害
smart enough, not good enough.
这世界
This world, it...
它一次次地打败你  直到你最终
it beats you up again and again until eventually, I...
大部分人  他们都
Most people, they just...
不再尝试了
they just stop trying.
但你不是那样的
But you're not like that.
你是个斗士
You're a fighter.
你一直都是
You always have been.
我真不知道你从谁那儿遗传来的
I honestly don't know where you get it from.
爸爸
Dad.
老实说  我觉得你是在医院被调包了
I think you were swapped in the hospital, to tell you the truth.
不
No.
我是遗传了你  妈妈
I get it from you, Mom.
是你
I get it from you.
不管是遗传了谁
Well, wherever you get it from,
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
为我被解雇骄傲吗
Proud of me for getting fired?
为你维护自己而骄傲
That you stood up for yourself.
你反抗了那些
That you stood up to those...
混蛋
shitheads.
妈妈
Mom!
是的  那些混蛋
Yes, those shitheads.
如果你真相信这则报道
And if you believe in this story...
看着我  南茜
Look at me, Nancy.
就去做完它
...finish it.
然后去卖给《印第安纳波利斯星报》什么的
Then go sell it to The Indianapolis Star or whatever and...
你能想象当他们在大报纸上
I mean, can you imagine their faces
读到自己小镇的报道时
when they read a story about their own town
会是什么表情吗
in a big paper like that?
那就..
That would be...
太了不起了
pretty amazing.
何不呢
So, why not?
Why not?
去做完
Finish it.
仅限维修人员
威尔
Uh, Will?
昨天的事
Um, you know, about yesterday...
没事的  卢卡斯
It's fine, Lucas.
你不用说什么
You don't have to say anything.
我知道  但是
I know, but it's just...
你的战役很不错
It was a really cool campaign.
迈克和我
And Mike and I,
-我们不该  -我现在不在乎了  卢卡斯
- we should've never-- - I don't care anymore, Lucas.
真的
I really don't.
我们现在有更重要的事要担心
We have bigger things to worry about now.
这应该关得住他了
This should hold him.
我找到断路器了
Hey, I found the breakers.
那玩意好吓人
Whoa, that thing is super creepy.
我看看
Let me see it.
这应该能行  是吧  伙计
I think this'll work. Right, buddy?
是啊  迈克
Right, Mike.
一一
Hey, El...
我就想说
I just wanted to say...
你记得我说奶奶病了吗
You know when I said Nana was sick?
她没病  我撒谎了
She wasn't. I lied.
-我知道  -嗯嗯  不
- I know. - Right, right, right. No, I just...
我觉得你必须知道为什么
think it was important for you to know the context.
霍普  他对我发狂了
Hopper, he went all crazy on me,
说我跟你泡在一起的时间太多了
telling me I'm spending way too much time with you.
他逼我撒谎的
He made me lie. I mean,
你是这世上对我最重要的人了
you're the most important thing to me in the world.
如果他是对的呢
What if he's right?
-什么  -霍普
- What? - Hop.
不不
No, no, no, no.
他就是讨厌欢乐的愤怒老头
He's just some angry old man who hates joy.
但如果我只见你
But if I only see you,
而我又跟你不是一个物种
and I'm a different species than you,
那我该多跟我同物种的人在一起
then I should be with my species more.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你监视我了吗
Did you spy on me?
-这是违反规定的  -我自己定规矩
- That's totally against the rules. - I make my own rules.
-迈克  你在吗  -嗯
- Mike, are you there? - Yeah!
-你们人呢  -我就来
- Where are you guys? - I'm coming. Just...
等一下的
hold on a second.
该死
Shit!
天呐  真希望不是你
God, I hope it's not you.
我真希望不是你
I really hope it's not you.
艾瑞卡  收到吗
Erica, do you copy?
我收到
I copy.
-你们这些呆子就位了吗  -我们就位了
- You nerds in position or what? - Yeah, we're in position.
这里一切安静  你可以开始了
It's all quiet here, so you've got the green light.
开始  收到
Green light, roger that.
威胁儿童安全行动开始
Commence Operation Child Endangerment.
能不能别那么喊
Can we maybe not call it that?
另一边见了
See you on the other side.
书呆子
Nerds.
温妮
Winnie!
温妮  是你吗
Winnie, is that you?
-拉里  -温妮  楼上  卧室
- Larry? - Winnie, upstairs in the bedroom!
宝贝
Baby.
天呐  宝贝  发生了什么
Oh, my God, baby, what happened?
给我拿部电话
Get me a phone.
-宝贝  -快给我拿部电话
- Baby-- - Get me a goddamn phone!
有发现吗
Anything?
没有
No.
这里没人
This place is dead.
好吧  接下来去哪
All right, where to next?
海斯农场
Hess Farm.
好了  书呆子们
All right, nerds.
我到了
I'm there.
你能看到什么吗
Do you-- Do you see anything?
嗯  你们特别关心的那些破盒子
Yeah, I see those boring boxes you're so excited about.
-有守卫吗  -没有
- Any guards? - Negative.
-陷阱呢  -如果看得到
- Booby traps? - If I could see them,
就不是好陷阱了
they'd be pretty shit traps,
-是不是  -多谢提醒
- wouldn't they? - Thank you for that.
我进去了
I'm in.
天呐
Oh, God.
免费冰淇淋
Free ice cream
终身享用
for life.
泳池关了
Pool's closed.
听到了吗
Do you hear me?
泳池关了
Pool is closed!
比利
Billy!
是谁
Who's there?
比利
Billy!
是谁
Who's there?
比利
Billy!
你觉得这好玩吗
You think this is funny, huh?
比利
Billy.
来找我
Come and find me.
我找到你  你就死定了
I find you, it is your funeral.
来抓我啊  来啊
Come and get me. Come on!
比利
Billy!
抓到你了
Got you.
来抓我啊  你个混蛋
Come and get me, you piece of shit.
你身后
Behind you.
开始
Now!
-快  -好了
- Come on. - Got it.
麦克斯
Max.
动手吧
Do it.
我是来见朵丽丝·德里斯科尔的
Uh, I'm here to see Doris Driscoll.
她好像是昨晚入院的
I think she was admitted last night.
姓名  关系
Name and relation?
南茜
Uh... Nancy...
德里斯科尔
Driscoll.
我是
I'm...
南茜·德里斯科尔
Nancy Driscoll.
她孙女
Her... granddaughter.
南茜·德里斯科尔
那绝对不是中餐
That's definitely not Chinese food.
你们最好  往后退退
Uh, maybe you guys should, you know, stand back.
-不  -就...
- No. - Just...
-退后点  -不
- Just step back, okay? - No.
-退后  真的  -不要
- Step back. Seriously. - No! No!
你死  我也死
If you die, I die.
好吧
Okay.
什么鬼
What the hell?
那是什么
What is that?
只有我觉得房间动了吗
Was that just me, or did the room move?
陷阱
Booby traps.
知道吗  拿上那个走吧
You know what? Let's just grab that and go.
我按哪个  艾瑞卡
Which one do I press, Erica?
快按按钮  呆子
Just press the damn button, nerd.
哪个  我按按钮了  好吗
Which one? I'm pressing the button, okay?
-按"开门"  -我按"开门"了
- Press "Open door." - I'm pressing "Open door."
打开...按别的按钮
Just open the-- Press the other button.
你们让开  让她去按
You guys, gut of the way so she can push the button--
-别闹了  -我在按呢
- Would you stop? - I'm trying.
让我做吧  别闹了
Would you let me just do it? Would you stop?
开门啊
Just open the door!
该死
Oh, shit.
麦克斯  放我出去
Max! Let me out of here!
放我出去
Let me out.
你们这些孩子
You kids...
你们觉得这好玩吗
You think this is funny?
你们是把这当成什么破恶作剧吗
You kids think this is some kind of sick prank, huh?
你们这些小混蛋觉得这好玩吗
You little shits think this is funny?
这是干什么
What is this?
开门
Open the door.
Open the door!
开门
快开门
Open the goddamn door!
到104了
We're at 220.
不是我的错
It's not my fault.
不是我的错  麦克斯
It's not my fault, Max.
真的不是我的错
I promise you, it's not my fault.
什么不是我的错  比利
What's not your fault, Billy?
我是做过些事  麦克斯
I've done things, Max. Really...
坏事
bad things.
但我不是有意的
I didn't mean to.
他逼我的
He made me do it.
谁逼你的
Who made you do it?
我不知道  就像个影子
I don't know, it's like a shadow.
就像个大影子
Like a giant shadow.
求你  麦克斯
Please, Max.
他都逼你做什么了
What did he make you do?
这不怪我  麦克斯  求你
It's not my fault, okay? Max, please.
求你  相信我  麦克斯  不怪我
Please, believe me, Max, it's not my fault.
我想阻止他了  真的
I tried to stop him, okay? I did.
相信我吧  麦克斯
Please believe me, Max.
相信我吧
Please believe me.
比利  你没事的
Billy, it's gonna be okay.
麦克斯  求你
Max, please.
没事的
It's gonna be okay.
我们想帮你
We want to help you.
你只需要告诉我们
You just have to talk to us, okay?
告诉我们
You have to talk to us.
我相信你  比利
I believe you, Billy.
我们一起想办法  好吗
We'll figure it out together, okay?
我能感觉到他
I can feel him.
-他被激活了  -我需要你相信我
- He's activated. - I need you to trust me. Please.
-麦克斯  离门远点  -什么
- Max, get away from the door. - What?
离门远点
Get away from the door!
放我出去  贱人
Let me out, you bitch! Let me out!
我砍死你
I'll fucking gut you!
放我出去
Let me out!
麦克斯  过来
Max, come on!
天呐
Oh, my God.
-他出不来吧  -不可能
- He can't get out, can he? - No way.
不可能
No way.
不
No!
不  不
No! No!
不
No!
No...
下地狱吧  你个混蛋
Go to hell, you piece of shit!
-那女孩  是她吗  -对
- The girl, was it her? - Yeah.
是她
It was her.
她知道了  她知道我了
She knows now. She knows about me.
她差点杀了我
She could've killed me.
是啊
Yes.
但杀不了我们
But not us.
杀不了我们
Not us.